export const QA =[
{question: "Q. Why should I use Pony Express?", answer : "A: To reduce the chances of you, or people in your community, getting sick. With the ongoing COVID-19 pandemic, grocery stores are overflowing with customers, who spend hours waiting in lines and risking transmission. Pony Express makes it so that you no longer need to leave the house to get groceries."},
{question: "Q. Is this a delivery service?", answer : "A: Yes, our algorithm matches consumers (in need of groceries) to drivers (who run grocery trips). For example, if you post a request for eggs, a driver in your community will be notified and add eggs to their shopping list and deliver them to your doorstep by the desired time."},
{question: "Q. How do I use this?", answer : "A: Watch our quick video (linked here)!"},
{question: "Q. Is it free to sign up?", answer : "A: Yes, it is free to sign up and use our platform!"},
{question: "Q. How is this any different from other grocery-delivery services?", answer : "A: PonyExpress was designed to foster community action and collaboration during this time of crisis. There is no service charge for placing a request, and your groceries will be delivered by a volunteer from your area. "},
{question: "Q. How do I use this?", answer : "A: Watch our quick video (linked here)!"},
{question: "Q. How can I trust the people making deliveries/posting orders? ", answer : "A: At the current stage, we are unable to enforce the transaction between the requester and the courier. We strongly recommend contacting the courier/requester beforehand to set up a time for dropoff and a payment method. "},
{question: "Q. How is payment handled? ", answer : "Payment is made from the recipient to the courier after the courier has made the purchase.  This means that the courier will temporary cover the cost of the purchase. We encourage contactless payment through Venmo or Paypal. However, both parties can also choose to use cash or any other methods of payment that suit them best."},
{question: "Q. Who determines how much I have to pay?", answer : "The courier will send a copy of the receipt that shows how much your purchase cost. You are encouraged to tip your courier, as they have likely driven a little out of their way to make the delivery, but tipping is not required."},
{question: "Q. What to do if I’m at risk?", answer : "When you’re placing a request, be sure to mark the check box “___(whatever the exact wording is)___” so that your request will be among the first ones shown when someone is offering to deliver. "},
{question: "Q. Can I use this if I'm sick?", answer : "If you have tested positive for COVID-19, have been exposed to COVID-19 or are feeling unwell, please refrain from making deliveries and stay at home. However, you may still post requests; just ensure that the delivery and payment methods are contactless in order to minimize the spread of any possible illness."},
{question: "Q. Can I cancel my order?", answer : "We encourage couriers not to cancel, but if they do, they should reach out to the recipient. All communication after the matching process is entirely in the hands of the users. "},
]
